how?
如何？
What and how?
什么以及如何？
Huang Zisheng.
Huang Zisheng.
We had a great time chatting.
我们聊得很开心。
I realized
我意识到
he is
他是
Very cheerful person.
非常开朗的人。
why do we use
我们为什么要使用
A cheerful person?
一个开朗的人？
Ask the spy.
询问间谍。
They choose it.
他们选择它。
if your attitude
如果你的态度
to others,
对他人，
no need
没有必要
Me becoming a lobbyist?
我成为说客？
Have you reminded him?
你提醒过他吗？
Let’s wait and see.
拭目以待吧。
tonight,
今晚，
Not eating yet?
还不吃饭？
I also have a bowl of instant noodles.
我还有一碗方便面。
I'll get it for you.
我去给你拿。
Your emotional intelligence is very high.
你的情商很高。
i will entertain you
我会招待你
Gram.
克吧。
Then I'll eat instant noodles.
那我就吃方便面吧。
Han Lie came in.
韩烈进来了。
Han Lie has accepted it.
韩烈已经接受了。
New mission letter.
新的使命信。
This seems to be
这好像是
He'll be making new moves soon.
他很快就会有新的举动。
After accepting the mission,
接受使命后，
Han Lie immediately ordered
韩烈立即下令
hotel room.
酒店房间。
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
Tomorrow evening.
明天晚上。
registered resident
登记居民
He was alone.
只有他一个人。
The elevator has arrived.
电梯到了。
Thanks.
谢谢。
why don't you take it
你为什么不拿走它
CCTV Hotel?
央视酒店？
The identity of the contact is not yet known.
联系人身份尚不清楚。
If he hides in a hotel
如果他躲在酒店里
There is a risk of being discovered.
会有被发现的危险。
Why?
为什么？
They have to come to the hotel to pick up the goods,
他们必须来酒店提货，
Still have to stay one night.
还是得留宿一晚。
have no idea.
不知道。
He is very relaxed.
他很放松。
then,
当时，
When is your vacation?
你的假期是什么时候？
You should know.
你应该知道。
After we broke up,
我们分手后，
Don’t you go on vacation anymore?
你不再去度假了吗？
impossible.
不可能的。
This is not a holiday.
这不是假期。
in this case,
在这种情况下，
No longer looking for a girlfriend?
不再找女朋友了吗？
Tanya.
坦尼娅。
just asking.
只是问问。
Liu, he's back.
刘，他回来了。
as a child,
作为一个孩子，
My home is near here.
我家就在这附近。
My sister often takes me here.
我姐姐经常带我来这里。
I'm the one causing this problem.
我就是造成这个问题的人。
Where is your sister?
你妹妹呢？
My brother can do whatever he wants
我哥哥做什么都行
Do better than me.
比我做得更好。
Only the person who truly loves you
只有真正爱你的人
who will continue to give to you
谁会继续给你
Chances of screwing up.
搞砸的机会。
perhaps.
或许。
you
你
tell your sister
告诉你姐姐
About the game?
关于游戏？
impossible.
不可能的。
This is our secret.
这是我们的秘密。
What should I tell him?
我该怎么告诉他呢？
He thought I would only bring trouble.
他认为我只会带来麻烦。
recently,
最近，
This happens.
发生这样的事情。
Maybe he's right.
也许他是对的。
I don't find it funny either.
我也不觉得好笑。
Just for fun, don't understand the specific situation.
娱乐一下，不了解具体情况。
Isn't it visible?
难道不可见吗？
Too hypocritical?
太虚伪了？
exit the game.
退出游戏。
Are you really not worried at all?
你真的一点都不担心吗？
Worry.
担心。
But we can’t sink deeper and deeper.
但也不能越陷越深。
but my heart
但我的心
Still a little uneasy.
还是有点不安。
Feeling guilty?
感到内疚？
Can you use nice words?
你能用好听的话吗？
and lost?
并丢失了？
We are the victims.
我们是受害者。
We are stuck.
我们被困住了。
Two young people tested negative.
两名年轻人呈阴性。
Consoling yourself after making a mistake?
犯错后安慰自己？
ways to entertain yourself
娱乐自己的方式
Won't come to the beach.
不会来海滩。
sigh.
叹。
I can't stand it either
我也受不了
Feeling sorry for myself here.
在这里为自己感到难过。
Tomorrow is the weekend,
明天就是周末了，
Do you still dare to go crazy?
你还敢发疯吗？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Across oceans.
跨越海洋。
Ayo.
阿哟。
Why doesn't he go to the elevator?
他为什么不去电梯？
Where did he go?
他去哪了？
The safe path is on the other side.
安全路径在另一边。
Batu.
巴图。
Ada.
艾达.
decided.
已定。
This is a safety line
这是安全线
Towards the roof.
朝向屋顶。
you check
你检查
Is there anyone else?
还有其他人吗
To the roof?
到屋顶？
OK
好的。
It's all over.
都结束了。
No one goes to the roof.
没有人去屋顶。
No receipts, no transactions.
没有收货，也没有交易。
So what can we do on the roof?
那么我们在屋顶上可以做什么呢？
roof?
屋顶？
military base.
军事基地。
Hang Lie is back.
杭烈回来了。
Come on, go up and have a look.
来吧，上去看看。
Do you think this signal tower
你认为这个信号塔
Is there anything special?
有什么特别的吗？
Opposite is the military headquarters.
对面是军事总部。
There is a host.
有一个主机。
There is a hard drive here.
这里有一个硬盘。
There is a hard drive.
有一个硬盘。
Be sure to have a camera.
一定要有相机。
The camera is here.
相机在这里。
Extraordinary.
非凡的。
There's a military base lurking here.
这里潜伏着一个军事基地。
is the best view.
是最好的观点。
This signal tower is built here.
这座信号塔就建在这里。
There must be something wrong.
一定有问题。
Han Lie stood up again.
韩烈又站了起来。
Ayo.
阿哟。
feels like my life
感觉就像我的生活
A new chapter will begin.
将开启新的篇章。
what are you kissing
你在接吻什么
don't you think
你不觉得
full
充满
About to run
即将运行
Feel the peak of life?
感受人生巅峰？
Young people like to fantasize, and that's a good thing.
年轻人喜欢幻想，这是好事。
This is where?
这是哪里？
Play with this.
玩这个。
Yes.
是的。
how?
如何？
Do you dare to play big?
你敢玩大吗？
How old?
多大？
In one round, everything is at stake.
在一轮比赛中，一切都岌岌可危。
stop.
休。
Don't dare.
不敢。
Why not?
为什么不敢？
Ayo.
阿哟。
You think, this round
你想，这一轮
Do we win or lose?
我们赢还是输？
I won.
我赢了。
I bet I lost.
我打赌我输了。
Who lost the bet?
谁输了赌注？
Very unfortunate.
非常不幸。
I won the bet, and I also won the other party.
我赌赢了，也赢了对方。
OK
好的。
If you can really win
如果真的能赢的话
Let me tell you a secret.
我告诉你一个秘密。
if i win,
如果我赢了，
I also have to tell you a secret.
我还要告诉你一个秘密。
agree.
同意。
What's the stakes?
赌注是什么？
I can bet.
我敢打赌。
strong.
壮。
it's your turn.
到你了。
I also gamble at the bank.
我也赌庄。
How can we make the same bet?
我们怎么能打同样的赌注呢？
If you want to keep it, you have to keep one too.
如果你想保留它，你也必须保留一个。
You're stupid, aren't you?
你很傻，不是吗？
Where are the contrarian bets?
反向投注在哪里？
besides,
除此之外，
We must win together.
我们必须共同胜利。
If you lose, lose together.
输了，一起输。
It seems I can't
看来我不能
Can't leave you.
无法离开你。
Open the card.
打开卡。
Relax a little, Zhuang.
放松一点，庄。
The villagers are not small.
庄人不小。
It seems we are both very lucky
看来我们俩都很幸运
Turning over is very difficult.
翻身是非常困难的。
This is fate.
这就是命运。
Ayo.
阿哟。
It's all over.
都结束了。
Duane Resort hides this.
杜安度假村隐藏了这一点。
camera.
相机。
He monitors the whole process
他全程监控
Military headquarters.
军事总部。
Now,
现在，
We solve two problems.
我们解决两个问题。
First,
第一的，
how do we prevent
我们如何预防
Was this video leaked?
这个视频泄露了？
Want to touch Han Lie?
想触摸韩烈吗？
second.
第二。
Find this camera.
找出这个相机。
Has Hangul been installed?
韩古尔安装了吗？
or
或者
other people?
其他人？
I think whoever installed the camera
我认为安装相机的人
Not necessarily Han Lie.
不一定是韩烈。
Through our previous investigation,
通过我们之前的调查，
he just
他只是
Who sends the message.
谁发送信息。
This research
这项研究
maybe not
也许不能
within a short period of time.
短时间内。
Okay, turn it back first.
好吧，先把它转回来。
Let’s solve Han Lie’s problem first.
先解决韩烈的问题。
OK
好的。
Hangyeol’s report notes show
Hangyeol的报告笔记显示
A batch of fresh food will be delivered in the afternoon.
下午会有一批生鲜食品送来。
Video images maybe
视频影像 也许
will be hidden inside and sent out.
将被隐藏在里面并被发送出去。
In order to prevent the secret video from being spread,
为了避免秘密视频被传播，
we must stop
我们必须停下来
Delivery of the Item.
该物品的交付。
but...
但...
this traffic route
这条交通路线
We have been paying attention for so long
我们关注了这么久
Grab it.
抓住它吧。
A little reluctantly.
有点不情愿。
Can you do it?
你们能做到吗？
so,
所以，
we take advantage of this opportunity
我们利用这个机会
melalui Hangyeol.
melalui Hangyeol.
we force it
我们强迫它
Boss Zhang is right behind him.
张老板就在他身后。
If this video
如果这个视频
Unable to send
无法发送
from sea routes.
来自海上航线。
Boss Zhang will definitely consider it
张老板一定会考虑的
Other methods.
其他方法。
Submit this video.
提交此视频。
so,
这样，
We can catch more fish.
我们可以钓更多的鱼。
OK
好的。
I called customs right away.
我马上打电话给海关。
Prevent Han Lie from going to sea.
阻止韩烈出海。
The system displays this item
系统显示此项目
not approved.
不批准。
But when I give it to me
但当我把它交给我的时候
Already approved.
已经批准了。
sorry.
对不起。
we can only
我们只能
Based on system results.
根据系统的结果。
An inspection was recently conducted.
近日进行了一次检查。
This is your item
这是您的物品
already taken.
已经采取。
We have to check everything.
我们必须检查一切。
Send the cargo to the checkpoint.
将货物送到检查站。
beautiful.
美好的。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
He started looking for help.
他开始寻求帮助。
Let’s see how Boss Zhang handles it.
看看张老板如何处理。
Han Jie didn’t send this thing.
韩杰没有送这个东西。
what happened?
发生了什么？
Customs inspection.
海关检查。
What a coincidence.
真是巧合。
When we send the goods,
当我们寄出货物时，
I feel unusual.
我感觉不寻常。
Do you think there are people from Guoan behind this?
你觉得背后有国安的人吗？
There is such a possibility.
有这样的可能性。
This line is very important to us.
这条线对我们来说非常重要。
So, we have to leverage relationships.
所以，我们必须利用关系。
Find out what happened.
找出发生了什么事。
Halo?
光环？
Secretary Zheng, it’s me.
郑秘书，是我。
what is it?
它是什么？
That's it.
就是这样。
have a friend
有一个朋友
Let me ask something.
让我问一些事情。
piece of cake?
小问题？
I think
我认为
No need to bother the leader anymore.
不用再麻烦领导了。
so,
所以，
Ask him.
请问他。
explain.
说。
This friend of mine
我的这个朋友
There are many goods that are subject to customs inspection.
有许多商品需要接受海关检查。
I want to ask,
我想问一下，
What is the specific reason?
具体原因是什么？
Send me the details.
把详细信息发给我。
I will get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快回复您。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Actually what?
其实什么？
what exactly is it?
到底是什么？
Have you never lost?
你没输过吗？
If you lose, there are no secrets anymore.
如果你输了，那就不再有秘密了。
I'm thinking,
我在想，
if you tell me
如果你告诉我
your secret,
你的秘密，
I'll tell you mine too.
我也告诉你我的。
Because you really keep your promise,
因为你真的信守承诺，
bet,
赌注，
Forget it.
把它忘了吧。
in this case,
在这种情况下，
what you really want to say
你真正想说的话
I would listen reluctantly.
我会不情愿地听。
Forget it.
把它忘了吧。
Did not you say
你不是说
Is everything doomed?
一切都是注定的吗？
Because we lost the bet,
因为我们赌输了，
maybe god
也许是上帝
make it impossible for us
让我们无法
Sharing too many secrets with each other.
彼此分享太多的秘密。
correct.
正确的。
This is all fate.
这都是命运。
So, let's save it first
那么，我们先保存一下
The secret is in my heart.
这个秘密在我心里。
to be honest.
说实话。
are you sorry
你对不起吗
Want to play with me?
和我一起玩吗？
if your partner is not me
如果你的伴侣不是我
Neither will you
你也不会
related to this issue.
涉及到这个问题。
regret.
后悔。
sorry.
对不起。
Why should I meet you?
我为什么要遇见你？
In the game?
在游戏里？
if
如果
Another way to meet,
另一种方式遇见，
You won't be so unlucky now.
现在就不会这么倒霉了。
Don't think too much.
别胡思乱想。
What went wrong was the game.
出了什么问题是游戏。
Can't blame anyone.
不能怪任何人。
besides,
除此之外，
Even without you,
即使没有你，
I can't escape either.
我也无法逃避。
this game
这个游戏
It is unknown how many people were injured.
不知道有多少人受伤。
As you said,
照你说的，
Are we going back to play?
我们要回去比赛了吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Don’t we all agree?
不是都同意了吗？
Quit the game together?
一起退出游戏？
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I feel like he's
我感觉他就像
A nightmare.
一个噩梦。
appears sometimes.
有时会出现。
I can't help but think about it.
我也不禁浮想联翩。
I always feel that this problem is definitely not solved.
我总感觉这个问题肯定没有解决。
Who are you,
你是，
So relaxing.
太放松了。
Very relaxing.
很放松。
Not playing games.
不玩游戏。
like
喜欢
There is no purpose.
没有目的。
Life has become very boring.
生活变得非常无趣。
Do you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
because of U.S
因为我们
In the game world.
在游戏世界中。
They are all gods.
都是神。
But in the real world,
但在现实世界中，
Instead, it does nothing.
相反，它什么也没做。
Been playing this game for a long time.
这个游戏已经玩了很长时间了。
Can't tell the difference anymore
再也无法分辨出区别了
Virtual and reality.
虚拟和现实。
Have we been hit?
我们被击中了吗
Game poison?
游戏毒？
what we lost
我们失去的
Not just a game,
不仅仅是一场游戏，
But escape to another world.
而是逃到另一个世界。
Give up your chance.
放弃自己的机会。
Look at them.
看他们。
They don't play.
他们不玩。
They are still alive.
他们还活着。
as long as you can accept it
只要你能接受
Boring life,
无聊的生活，
enough.
足够了。
in this case...
在这种情况下...
Not really.
并不真地。
Incidentally,
顺便一提，
Do you have any other goals?
你还有其他目标吗？
or
或者
Or dream.
或梦想。
There were a lot of people like that when I was a kid
我小的时候有很多这样的人
When you grow up, you no longer have it.
长大了就没有了。
my dream first
我的梦想先
Saving the world.
正在拯救世界。
so?
所以？
I realize now that I
我意识到我现在
Puzzled.
困惑。
More than 20 years later,
20多年后，
Not only can I not save the world,
我不但无法拯救世界，
I may still need
我可能还需要
Saved by this world.
被这个世界拯救了。
I feel the same way.
我也有这样的感觉。
I'm very depressed now
我现在很沮丧
You must use gambling to numb yourself.
必须用赌博来麻痹自己。
Use betting
使用投注
with bets.
与赌注。
As you said,
照你说的，
Do we want to live like this?
我们要这样生活吗？
so?
所以？
Can you really become Superman?
你真的能成为超人吗？
Superman is definitely not.
超人绝对不是。
But at least,
但至少，
we can still do it
我们仍然可以做到
Something meaningful.
一些有意义的事情。
For example?
例如？
Just like now.
就像现在一样。
You can do it first.
可以先做。
And try not to cause trouble to the country.
并尽量不要给国家添麻烦。
And you?
你呢？
What are your next plans?
您接下来的计划是什么？
maybe one day
也许有一天
I'm leaving Jinhai.
我要离开金海了。
where to?
去哪儿？
Back to Los Angeles.
回到洛杉矶。
I didn't have any plans at first
一开始我也没有打算
Stay in Jinhai.
留在金海。
It turns out you are in Jinhai
原来你在金海
for
为了
mission accomplished.
完成任务。
correct.
正确的。
In order to meet you,
为了遇见你，
Play games with you.
和你一起玩游戏。
I know it's a lie
我知道这是谎言
But I'm glad to hear it.
但我很高兴听到这个消息。
You drank too much.
你喝太多了。
Not drunk.
没有醉。
Have you ever heard a saying?
你听过一句话吗？
The more I realize it, the more ridiculous I find it.
越是意识到，就越觉得可笑。
I want
我想要
Should I go back to racing?
我应该回去比赛吗？
No.
不。
Didn’t you just ban me?
你刚才不是禁止我了吗？
Bring this up?
提出这个？
Why do you say that yourself?
为什么你自己这么说？
They deceived me.
他们欺骗了我。
I lost miserably.
我输得很惨。
Where did I lose?
我哪里输了？
Where should I win?
我应该赢在哪里？
You are really drunk.
你真的醉了。
you lose
你输了
At the casino.
在赌场。
Not in the game.
不在游戏中。
I don't mean money.
我指的不是钱。
so what?
所以呢？
you.
你。
You are really drunk.
你真的醉了。
cheers.
干杯。
No.
不。
as far as I know,
据我所知，
Customs receives report
海关收到报告
Your store is suspected of smuggling.
你们店涉嫌走私。
smuggling?
走私？
Who reported it?
谁举报的？
Have you ever offended anyone?
你曾经冒犯过任何人吗？
No.
不。
Customs will be keeping a close eye on you these days.
这些天海关会密切关注你。
For security reasons,
出于安全原因，
all tasks in this row
该行中的所有任务
Stop first.
先停下来。
We'll decide later.
我们稍后再决定。
Where is the cargo?
货物呢？
I'll send someone to get it.
我会派人去取。
and sent from another line.
并从另一条线路发送。
OK
好的。
Hello, Director Huang.
黄主任您好。
Hello Hello hello.
你好你好你好。
Welcome to Macau.
欢迎来到澳门。
I'm also looking forward to it.
我也非常期待。
this seminar.
这次研讨会。
Very good, very good, very good.
很好，很好，很好。
Please sit inside.
请坐里面。
OK
好的。
Hang Lie leaves.
杭烈离开。
He went to church again.
他又去了教堂。
Most likely he accepted
很有可能他接受了
New mission.
新使命。
Do you think he's going to hand it over?
你认为他会去交接吗？
perhaps.
或许。
Customs clearance cannot be carried out.
无法进行清关。
He must choose another path.
他必须选择另一条路。
Hope it will show up this time
希望这次能出现
It's Boss Zhang.
是张老板。
Already arrived.
已经到了。
Tuan Yu.
Tuan Yu.
The laboratory has sent it
实验室已经发了
B13 ingredient analysis.
B13成分分析。
The B13 sample we got
我们拿到的B13样品
and the form of this composition
以及这个组合物的形式
All the same.
全部都一样。
But there are still some
但还是有一些
Slightly different.
稍微不一样。
The difference is very small.
差别很小。
We suspect this sample
我们怀疑这个样本
problem appear
出现问题
there is a question.
有一个问题。
Or he's not
或者他不是
Latest research results.
最新研究成果。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
I received a sample of B13.
我收到了 B13 样品。
there is a question.
有一个问题。
Not a final sample.
不是最终样品。
What do you think the problem is?
您认为问题出在哪里？
The person who handles the sample,
处理样品的人，
ada Yu Xiaoyue.
ada Yu Xiaoyue.
Shi Lei.
Shi Lei.
dan Han Jie.
dan Han Jie.
It can't be Yu Xiaoyue.
不可能是于小月。
He didn't get the original sample.
他没有得到原始样本。
There was no reason for him to commit suicide.
他没有理由自杀。
Shi Leidan Han Jie
Shi Lei dan Han Jie
Also a possibility
也有可能
Do something during transmission.
在传输过程中做某事。
Shi Lei has already gone out.
石磊已经出去了。
Han Jie is one of his own.
韩杰是他自己人。
He had no reason to take samples.
他没有理由取样。
Then sit quietly.
然后静静地坐着。
There is another possibility.
还有一种可能。
you mean,
你的意思是，
What are the Gook-an people doing?
Gook-an人在做什么？
This is the worst case scenario.
这是最糟糕的情况。
if this is true
如果这是真的的话
Our transportation route is in Zhenhai
我们的交通路线是在镇海
most likely
最有可能的
under their supervision.
在他们的监督下。
Han Lie's situation is very dangerous.
韩烈的情况非常危险。
National Security Agency.
国家安全局。
He may have been watched.
他可能已经被监视了。
You have to be careful.
你必须要小心。
OK
好的。
say.
说话。
Han Lie was discovered.
韩烈被发现了。
He knows too much.
他知道的太多了。
It cannot fall into the hands of Guoan.
不能落入国安手中。
Find a way to save it.
找到一种方法来保存它。
OK
好的。
Halo?
光环？
You're caught.
你被抓住了。
Someone is coming to pick you up. Come on.
有人来接你了，快走吧。
Han Lie has already come down.
韩烈已经下来了。
That motorcycle.
那辆摩托车。
damaged.
损坏的。
my car!
我的车！
stop!
停止！
He has already run away, so hurry up and chase him.
他已经跑了，你赶紧去追吧。
Ignore him for now.
暂时不理他。
Sooner or later you will catch it.
迟早你会抓住它。
What about you, hard drive?
你呢，硬盘？
I think my foot dropped.
我想我的脚掉下来了。
Your head is dizzy, isn't it?
你的头很晕，是吗？
A little dizzy.
有点头晕。
Ayo.
阿哟。
This guy.
这家伙。
Is he Boss Zhang?
他是张老板吗？
Boss Zhang’s information,
张老板的信息，
He's a little fuzzy.
他有点模糊。
We can't be sure either.
我们也不能确定。
He always wears a helmet.
他总是戴着头盔。
I can't see his face.
我看不到他的脸。
I appreciate it.
我很感激。
Wu Xi took the hard drive.
吴熙拿走了硬盘。
Why was Wu Xi injured?
吴熙怎么受伤了？
He's fine.
他没事。
Now.
现在。
Under examination at the hospital.
正在医院接受检查。
Di mana Hangyeol?
Di mana Hangyeol?
Now is our only clue.
现在是我们唯一的线索。
we have to find a way
我们必须找到办法
Find it.
找到它。
of.
的。
We were at his place.
我们当时在他的住处。
and Tuna King Shop.
和金枪鱼王店。
Everyone is looking at him.
每个人都在看着他。
OK
好的。
game account
游戏账号
Still there too
也还在那里
within our regulatory scope.
在我们的监管范围内。
As long as he comes in,
只要他进来，
We'll find out.
我们会知道的。
Also, check him out.
另外，检查一下他。
All online transaction records.
所有网上交易记录。
see if we can
看看我们是否可以
Find his hiding place.
找到他的藏身之处。
You are like ports and docks.
你就像港口和码头。
This all needs investigation.
这一切都需要调查。
He knows this area very well.
他非常了解这个领域。
The main investigation concerns him.
主要调查与他有关。
with him.
和他一起。
Fishermen and traders.
渔民和商人。
Chief Qin.
秦科长。
This operation failed.
本次操作失败，
I have a great responsibility.
我有很大的责任。
Your choice is correct.
你的选择是正确的。
I would do the same thing.
我也会做同样的事情。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
besides,
除此之外，
who installed
谁安装了
Who installed it?
谁安装的？
Inside the Duane Hotel.
杜安酒店内。
most likely
最有可能的
A spy has infiltrated.
有间谍潜入。
this line.
这条线。
You should continue to investigate.
你们应该继续调查。
understand.
理解。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
Are you awake?
你醒着么？
I have a headache.
我头疼。
Drink water first.
先喝水。
Thanks.
谢谢。
do you remember
你是否记得
What did you say to me yesterday?
你昨天对我说什么了？
What?
什么？
your secret.
你的秘密。
What secret?
什么秘密？
explain.
说。
Do you want to get back into the game?
你想回到游戏吗？
What else did I tell you?
我还告诉你什么了？
what else?
还有什么？
Contribute to the country.
为国家做出贡献。
Isn't this a mistake?
这不是驴唇不对马嘴吗？
play games.
玩游戏。
what is the relationship
有什么关系
Contribute to the country?
为国家做贡献？
Who knows what you mean?
谁知道你的意思？
We'll meet again.
我们再见面。
Our flagship agency.
我们的旗舰代理商。
We're all out.
我们都出局了。
in life,
在生活中，
There are always some things that cannot be done.
总有一些事情是做不到的。
this is your room
这是你的房间
too small.
太小。
I'll change it for you to a bigger one.
我给你们换个大的。
unnecessary.
不需要。